<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<TestCases xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<TestCaseMetaData id="EHR Test Plan" date="2/18/2016" name="EHR Test Plan" version="20160218">
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<Notes>To support real-time dynamic testing, the Tester at their discretion, may selectively modify result report data prior to importing the test message into the EHR technology.
The test data for MSH.21 demonstrates the use of profile components; the system-under-test may alternatively use the post or pre-coordinated profile identifier(s).</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the EHR test plan.  It involves display and incorporation verification at different levels (see juror document for details). </Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="GU" date="2/18/2016" name="GU" version="20160218">
		<Comments>This is the Globally Unique Profile Component (GU) test case group - all identifiers in these test cases use OIDs to identify the assigning authority.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="PT and INR - GU" date="2/18/2016" name="PT and INR Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers a simple electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  The EHR-S receives and incorporates the messages, and creates and sends an acknowledgement message.  The LIS system receives the acknowledgement message.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate capability to support minimally populated messages (single occurrences of all required ("R") elements).</TestObjectives>
		<Comments>The initial test plan is a "smoke test" to reveal simple failures  severe enough to preclude further testing.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_0.0_1.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Smoke test" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. Hector Ramos is a 81 year old Hispanic male who is on warfarin therapy.  Mr. Ramos presents to  Good Health Clinic to see Dr. Radon for a routine check up.   The doctor orders a Prothrombin Time (PT + INR) test from the clinical lab at Century Hospital using the clinic's EHR system and instruct Mr. Ramos to go to the laboratory's patient service center to have the blood sample collected.   The laboratory performs the requested test and the final result was  10.5  sec with a ref range of 9.5-13.8 sec  and the INR calculated to be 1.0    {INR}   with a  normal reference range being 0.8 and 1.2 {INR}.  The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the Good health Clinic's EHR system.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Minimally populated message.
Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate all required data elements for the test case:
Minimally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSH segment.
Minimally populated PID Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the PID segment.
Minimally populated ORC Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the ORC segment.
Minimally populated OBR Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the OBR segment.
Minimally populated OBX Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the OBX segment.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>No Notes.</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the "smoke test" - testing basic functionality and support for all Required elements per the LRI IG to reveal simple failures severe enough to preclude further testing..</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="ACK_0.0_3.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Smoke test ACK" version="20160218">
		<Description>Dr Radon's EHR-S transmits an accept acknowledgement message to Century Hospital's LIS which indicates the ORU message Prothrombin Time (PT + INR) test results has been successfully received.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>No Post-Condition.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Minimally populated message.
Demonstrate capability to support creating a positive accept acknowledgment Message in response to successful receipt of the ORU message:
Minimally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSH segment.
Minimally populated MSA Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSA segment.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>No Notes.</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the initial "smoke testing" to reveal simple failures of the acknowledgment message severe enough to preclude further testing.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="ACK_0.0_4.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Smoke test App ACK" version="20160218">
		<Description>Dr Radon's EHR-S  transmits an application acknowledgement message to Century Hospital's LIS which indicates the ORU message Prothrombin Time (PT + INR) test results has been successfully parsed and incorporated.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>Test message for ACK_0.0_5.1-NG will be created.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Minimally populated message.
Demonstrate capability to support creating a positive application acknowledgment Message in response to successful receipt of the ORU message:
Minimally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSH segment.
Minimally populated MSA Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSA segment.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>No Notes.</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the initial "smoke testing" to reveal simple failures of the application acknowledgment message severe enough to preclude further testing.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="ACK_0.0_5.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Smoke test ACK to AppACK" version="20160218">
		<Description>Century Hospital's LIS transmits an accept acknowledgement message to Dr Radon's EHR-S which indicates the Application Acknowledgement message has been successfully received.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>No Post-Condition.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Minimally populated message.
Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate all required data elements for the accept acknowledgement test case:
Minimally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSH segment.
Minimally populated MSA Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSA segment.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>To support real-time dynamic testing, the Tester at their discretion, may selectively modify result acknowledgement data prior to importing the test message into the EHR technology.</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the initial "smoke testing" to reveal simple failures of the acknowledgment message severe enough to preclude further testing.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Sed Rate-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Sed Rate" version="20160218">
		<Description>These test plans are designed to test capability to process maximally populated message (all the R, RE, C(a/b) elements defined in the implementation guide), the progression from a 'final' to 'corrected' report, and to report the test was not performed due to a specimen quality issue.</Description>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to corrected-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to corrected header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  The EHR-S receives and incorporates  the message.   These test plans are designed to test capability to process maximally populated message (all the elements defined in the implementation guide)  as well as the progression from a "final" to "corrected" report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate capability to support maximally populated messages - all supported (R,RE,C(a/b)) elements including multiple occurrences of repeating elements.
Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final and  corrected results message.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_1.0_1.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with pain, swelling, and redness in several joints including his elbows, wrists, knees, and hips. In order to screen for rheumatoid diseases, Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered an erythrocyte sedimentation rate (ESR or Sed Rate) blood test using the Good Health Clinic's EHR system,  specifying that the laboratory's patient service center was to draw the blood specimen from the patient later that same day.  Dr Radon also requests that the results be CC'd to Dr Pafford M. Hamlin Sr, a specialist to which he is referring Mr. Jones as well as Dr. Daniel Davison who is Mr. Jones' regular doctor.
The laboratory performs the requested test and the final result was 10 mm/hr, a normal value with the normal reference range being 0-17 mm/hr. The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the Good health Clinic's EHR system used in Dr. Radon's office practice on the same day.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Maximally populated message.
Demonstrate ability to  import and incorporate all supported relevant (R,RE,C(a/b)) data elements for the test case, including multiple occurrences:
Demonstrate the capability to support Timing_Qty Group and Timing/Quantity Segment (TQ1).
Demonstrate the capability to support Notes and Comments Segments (NTE) that follow the Observation Request Segment (OBR), including multiple occurrences.
Maximally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the MSH segment.
Maximally populated PID Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the PID segment. 
Maximally populated NTE segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including proper handling of formatted text.
Maximally populated ORC Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the ORC segment.
Maximally populated OBR Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the OBR segment. 
Maximally populated SPM Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements in the SPM segment. 
Maximally populated TQ1 Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the TQ1 segment .
Specific test points include the use of the NM data type for OBX.2, the value of "10" for results (OBX.5), the value of "N" for abnormal flags (OBX.8), and the observation results status is "F" (OBX.11).</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>In addition to the review of all elements, check that the Notes after the order are properly formatted and displayed.</Notes>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_1.0_2.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="corrected" version="20160218">
		<Description>Based on LRI_1.0_Sed_Rate and LRI_1.1_Sed_Rate:
Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with pain, swelling, and redness in several joints including his elbows, wrists, knees, and hips. In order to rule out rheumatoid arthritis, Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered an erythrocyte sedimentation rate (ESR or Sed Rate) blood test to be performed, specifying that the laboratory was to draw the blood specimen from the patient the same day. The final result of this test was 10 mm/hr, a normal value with the normal reference range being 0-17 mm/hr. The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice later that same day.

The ESR test instrument was recalibrated and the ESR specimen was re-analyzed. After the recalibration and re-analysis, the result value for Mr. Jones' ESR test changed from 10 mm/hr to 20 mm/hr. A Corrected result report with a result value of 20 mm/hr and an abnormal flag of "H" was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and LRI_1.0_1.1-GU has been previously received by the EHR-S and incorporated with the patient's record.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the ability to update the patient record based on corrected results.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_1.0-GU_Sed_Rate_Final test case prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status – now C instead of F (OBR-25)
Result date/time is later than before (OBR-22)
Result for Sed Rate changed from 10 to 20 (OBX-5), which changed the interpretation (OBX-8) from N to H and result status (OBX-11) is C
An additional comment (NTE after OBX) is displayed at the result level, indicating: "Specimen re-analyzed per request of ordering provider."</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11 for a corrected result.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Specimen rejected-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Specimen rejected header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  The EHR system receives and incorporates an electronic lab result message.    This test plan is designed to test capability to process a report in which a test was not performed due to a specimen quality issue.</Description>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate capability to report the test was not performed due to a specimen quality issue.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_1.2_1.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="specimen rejection" version="20160218">
		<Description>Ms. Janet Anderson is a 26 year old white female who presented with fever of unknown origin and generalized joint pain. In order to rule out infection and autoimmune disease, Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered an erythrocyte sedimentation rate (ESR or Sed Rate) blood test to be performed. A blood specimen for the ESR test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab for processing. The analysis could not be performed because the specimen arrived clotted. No result value could be obtained. A Specimen Rejection message for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to import and incorporate a valid Rejected Specimen message.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Since the specimen was rejected there is no lab result in the Juror Document; there is however specimen reject information that needs to be displayed.
This test case requires display verification only. 
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status (OBR-25) is X 
Information about the specimen condition (SPM-24) and reject reason (SPM-21)
A result value (OBX-5) showing that the test could not be performed with attached comment (NTE after OBX) as explanation.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case tests handling of specimen rejection.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="CBC" date="2/18/2016" name="CBC header" version="20160218">
		<Description>These test plans are designed to test capability to process  the progression from a 'partial' to 'final'  report, from a 'final'  to 'wrong patient' report, as well as from a 'final'  to 'amended' report.</Description>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Partial result to final-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Partial result to final header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.    This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process the progression from a "partial" to "final" report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a partial and final results message.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_2.0_0.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="partial" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a history of fever, fatigue, and shortness of breath on exertion. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a complete blood count (CBC) test to be performed. A blood specimen for the CBC test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The laboratory director at this hospital is Dr. Phil J. Knowsalot, III. The blood specimen was analyzed, and before all of the results are available a partial report is generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to Dr. Hamlin Pafford.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to import and incorporate a valid LRI CBC panel result that contains some, but not all of the result values for the expected OBX segments.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only.</Notes>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_2.0_1.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a history of fever, fatigue, and shortness of breath on exertion. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a complete blood count (CBC) test to be performed. A blood specimen for the CBC test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The laboratory director at this hospital is Dr. Phil J. Knowsalot, III. The blood specimen was analyzed, and before all of the results are available a partial report is generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to  Dr. Hamlin Pafford.

The next day the all results of the CBC test are available and a final report is generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to Dr. Hamlin Pafford.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test Case LRI_2.0_0.1-GU message has been received and incorporated into the EHR-S.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to update the patient record based on additional results received in the report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_2.0_0.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from A to F
The 9 previously empty results now have results (OBX-5), interpretations (OBX-8) and status (OBX-11) has changed from I to F</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to wrong patient-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to wrong patient header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process the progression from a "final" to "wrong patient" report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final result message and handle report that the initial final result was sent for the wrong patient.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_2.1_1.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="final_Wrong" version="20160218">
		<Description>The laboratory at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA 90067 received a blood specimen from Dr. Radon's office on patient Willow A. Jones for a complete blood count (CBC) test.  The patient was identified in the system as a 14 year old white female.  The blood specimen was analyzed and the final result revealed critically high WBC of 32,000/uL.   Dr. Radon was notified of the critical result by phone and the laboratory included the following comment in the report , "Critically high WBC reported to Dr. Radon by phone the day of the report." The final test result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to import and incorporate a final valid LRI CBC panel result message</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_2.1_2.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Corrected_Wrong" version="20160218">
		<Description>The laboratory at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA 90067 received a blood specimen from Dr. Radon's office on patient Willow A. Jones for a complete blood count (CBC) test.  The patient was identified in the system as a 14 year old white female.  The blood specimen was analyzed and the final result revealed critically high WBC of 32,000/uL.   Dr. Radon was notified of the critical result by phone and the laboratory included the following comment in the report , "Critically high WBC reported to Dr. Radon by phone the day of the report." The final test result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office.

The following morning, Dr. Radon upon review of results noticed several anomalies with the results and notified the lab. The lab traced the issue back to mislabeled specimens and reissued the report as corrected, indicating that the results were reported on the wrong patient.  The laboratory included a comment, stating, "All results previously reported for this patient were reported in error; they do not apply to this patient."</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_2.1_1.1-GU message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to update the patient record when corrected results indicate the prior results were for the wrong patient.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_2.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C
An additional comment (NTE after OBR) is displayed under the Order
All result values (OBX-5) are “”, without interpretation (OBX-8) and Result Status (OBX-11) has changed from F to W</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11 and the proper handling of OBX-5 values when indicating the prior results were reported for the wrong patient.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to Amended-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to Amended header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.    This test plan is designed to test the EHR-S' capability to process the progression from a "final" to "amended" report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final and amended results message.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Use of the amended result status code 'A" is permitted, so this test case constitutes an optional test case, should partners agree to support this concept.</Notes>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_3.1_1.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="final_amended" version="20160218">
		<Description>The laboratory at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA 90067 received a blood specimen from Dr. Radon's office on patient Willow C. Jones for a complete blood count (CBC) test.  The patient was identified in the system as a 14 year old white female.  The blood specimen was analyzed and the final result revealed high WBC, particularly Lymphocytes and Neutrophils as well as high hematocrit, MCV and MCH. The final test result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office. </Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to import and incorporate a final valid LRI CBC panel result message</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_3.1_2.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Corrected_Amended" version="20160218">
		<Description>The laboratory at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA 90067 received a blood specimen from Dr. Radon's office on patient Willow C. Jones for a complete blood count (CBC) test.  The patient was identified in the system as a 14 year old white female.  The blood specimen was analyzed and the final result revealed high WBC, particularly Lymphocytes and Neutrophils as well as high hematocrit, MCV and MCH. The final test result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office.

The following morning, Dr. Radon upon review of results noticed that the Willow's Date of birth was listed as 12/27/2001, but Willow is only 4 years old, not 14. Dr. Radon notified the lab to correct the Date of Birth to 12/27/2010. The lab reviewed the results and adjusts the normal ranges for the observations based on on the updated age from adult reference ranges to 4 year old and re-issued the report as amended, leaving only the elevated WBC, with increased Neutrophils and a low hemoglobin as abnormal results.  The laboratory included a comment, stating, "The patient's DOB was corrected by request of the ordering provider. The normal ranges are based on age group and so were adjusted accordingly for most of these observations, which led to a change in interpretations of existing results. Please review all interpretations in detail."</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_3.1_1.1-GU message has previously been sent.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to update the patient record when interpretations and reference ranges were changed due to demographic information updates in an amended report.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_2.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C
An additional comment (NTE after OBR) is displayed under the Order
No change to Result value (OBX-5), but changes to Reference Ranges (OBX-7) in most cases,  interpretation (OBX-8) in some (hemoglobin, hematocrit, MCV, MCH, Lymphocytes) and Result Status (OBX-11) has changed from F to A, where changes have occurred.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11for results in an amended report.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Lipid Panel-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Lipid Panel Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  These test plan are designed to test the system's capability to process reports containing "Ask at Order Entry Questions (AOEs)" and handle receipt of duplicate messages.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a message that contains an Ask at Order Entry Questions (AOEs) and to demonstrate the proper handling of receipt of duplicate reports.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_3.0_1.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="initial result - final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented for a cardiology exam. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a lipid panel test to be performed to check for hyperlipidemia. A blood specimen for the lipid panel test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The laboratory director at this hospital is Dr. Phil J. Knowsalot, III. The blood specimen was analyzed, and the final result of the lipid panel test showed that all components were within the normal range. The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to Dr. Pafford M. Hamlin, Sr.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to import and incorporate a valid LRI message for a lipid panel blood test lab result.
Demonstrate ability to support Ask at Order Entry Questions.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only. 
Concentrate on the following areas:  
Answers for Ask at Order Entry questions (OBX-5) are distinguished from the results for the same order.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the handling of Ask at Order Entry questions as part of a typical Lipid Panel.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_3.0_2.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="duplicates" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented for a cardiology exam. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a lipid panel test to be performed to check for hyperlipidemia. A blood specimen for the lipid panel test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The laboratory director at this hospital is Dr. Phil J. Knowsalot, III. The blood specimen was analyzed, and the final result of the lipid panel test showed that all components were within the normal range. The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to Dr. Pafford M. Hamlin, Sr.

A duplicate report of the report is sent shortly after the first.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_3.0_1.1-GU message has been received and incorporated into the EHR-S.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the proper handling of receipt of duplicate reports.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_3.0_1.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only and is testing how the EHR-S behaves when it gets the exact same report.

</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the handling of duplicate reports based on OBR-22 comparison.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Culture and Suscep-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Culture and Suscep Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>These test plans are designed to test capability to process the progression from a 'preliminary' to 'final' to 'corrected' microbiology report.</Description>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a preliminary, final, and corrected result microbiology message.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Preliminary result-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Preliminary result Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S. This test plan tests the systems' capability to process  a "preliminary" microbiology Culture and Sensitivity report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a preliminary result microbiology message.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.0_1.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="preliminary result" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing.  The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the EHR-S can correctly incorporate a valid typically populated message for a preliminary Stool Culture microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Result Report Status (OBR-25) is P 
3 different results (OBX-5) and their interpretations (OBX-8) for the same test are properly displayed with a Result Status (OBX-11) of P</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to corrected (FRU)-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to corrected (FRU) Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The EHR system receives and incorporates an electronic lab result message.    This test plan and the previous test plan are designed to test the EHR-S' capability to process the progression from a "preliminary" to "final" to "corrected" microbiology Culture and Sensitivity reports.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final and corrected result microbiology message when the filler order number uniquely identifies the test ordered. (FRU profiles).</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.1_2.1-GU_FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="prelim to final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing.  The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-GU message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for a final Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from P to F
3 different results (OBX-5) and their interpretations (OBX-8) for the same test are properly displayed; Result Status (OBX-11) changed from P to F
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.
</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.1_3.1-GU_FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="final to corrected" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.

Five hours later the laboratorian realizes that the result in the susceptibility suite for Shigella Flexneri was wrong and corrects the report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-GU AND LRI_4.1_2.1-GU_FRU messages have been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for a corrected Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU and LRI_4.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).
For the susceptibility test on Shigella flexneri the Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C - ensure the related results show:
For the test identified as "Ampicillin" the result (OBX-5) changed from 16ug/mL to 32ug/mL and interpretation (OBX-8) from "I" to "R" and the Result Status (OBX-11) changed from F to C.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.1_4.1-GU_FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="final to corrected/Appended" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.

Five hours later the laboratorian realizes that the result in the susceptibility suite for Shigella Flexneri were missing results for additional antibiotic.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-GU AND LRI_4.1_2.1-GU_FRU messages have been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for an appended Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU and LRI_4.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).
For the susceptibility test on Shigella flexneri the Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C - ensure the related results show:
additional tests have been appended, i.e. are new: 
Result (OBX-5) and interpretation (OBX-8) for "Trimethoprim+Sulfamethoxazole" and "Ciprofloxacin".</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to corrected (FRN)-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to corrected (FRN) Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The EHR system receives and incorporates an electronic lab result message.    This test plan and the previous test plan are designed to test the EHR-S' capability to process the progression from a "preliminary" to "final" to "corrected" microbiology Culture and Sensitivity reports.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final and corrected result microbiology message when the filler order number does not uniquely identifies the test ordered. (FRN profiles).</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.2_2.1-GU_FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="prelim to final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing.  The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-GU message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for a final Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from P to F
3 different results (OBX-5) and their interpretations (OBX-8) for the same test are properly displayed; Result Status (OBX-11) changed from P to F
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.
</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.2_3.1-GU_FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="final to corrected" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.

Five hours later the laboratorian realizes that the result in the susceptibility suite for Shigella Flexneri was wrong and corrects the report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-GU AND LRI_4.2_2.1-GU_FRN messages have been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for a corrected Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU and LRI_4.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).
For the susceptibility test on Shigella flexneri the Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C - ensure the related results show:
For the test identified as "Ampicillin" the result (OBX-5) changed from 16ug/mL to 32ug/mL and interpretation (OBX-8) from "I" to "R" and the Result Status (OBX-11) changed from F to C.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.2_4.1-GU_FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="final to corrected/Appended" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.

Five hours later the laboratorian realizes that the result in the susceptibility suite for Shigella Flexneri were missing results for additional antibiotic.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-GU AND LRI_4.2_2.1-GU_FRN messages have been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for an appended Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU and LRI_4.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).
For the susceptibility test on Shigella flexneri the Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C - ensure the related results show:
additional tests have been appended, i.e. are new: 
Result (OBX-5) and interpretation (OBX-8) for "Trimethoprim+Sulfamethoxazole" and "Ciprofloxacin".</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Reflex Hepatitis-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex Hepatitis header" version="20160218">
		<Description>This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process reflex test reports which use the parent/child reporting structure.</Description>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Parent child(FRU)-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Parent child(FRU) Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.   This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process reflex test reports which use the parent/child reporting structure.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a reflex result message when the filler order number uniquely identifies the test ordered. (FRU profiles).</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_5.0_1.1-GU_FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex" version="20160218">
		<Description>A patient is hospitalized for substance abuse. The physician orders a hepatitis panel through the hospital's EHR system to test for Hepatitis A, B and C antibodies/antigens. The serum specimen is collected the same day at in the morning and submitted to the hospital lab for testing via their LIS right after it was drawn. A few hours later the patient's test results are as follows:
 (1)Hepatitis A IgM antibodies (IgM anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (2)Hepatitis A antibodies (anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (3)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) "Negative"
 (4)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) quantitative 0.40 IU/mL (reference range: &lt;0.50 IU/mL)
 (5)Hepatitis B virus e antibodies (anti-HBVe) "Negative"
 (6)Hepatitis B surface antigen (HBVsAg) "Negative"
 (7)Hepatitis B surface antibody (anti-HBVs) "Negative"
 (8)Hepatitis C antibody screen (anti-HCV) "Positive"
 (9)Hepatitis C antibodies Signal to Cut-off Ratio 10.8 s/co (reference range: 0.0-0.9 s/co)
The hospital LIS sends an LRI message containing these results to the EHR-S. </Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability to import and incorporate a typically populated Hepatitis Panel lab result message.
Tests support for multiple comments for one test result.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Proper display of the results (OBX-5) with structured numeric format (#4 and 9) with interpretations (OBX-8) 
Comments for result of the lab result identified as "Hepatitis C virus Ab Signal/Cutoff in Serum or Plasma by Immunoassay" is properly grouped with its result.
Results for the Reflex test are properly associated with the result that spawned its creation, which is the detection of Hepatitis C virus Antibody in Serum, as part of the Hepatitis A B C Panel screen.
</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the parent message.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_5.0_2.1-GU-FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex" version="20160218">
		<Description>A patient is hospitalized for substance abuse. The physician orders a hepatitis panel through the hospital's EHR system to test for Hepatitis A, B and C antibodies/antigens. The serum specimen is collected the same day at in the morning and submitted to the hospital lab for testing via their LIS right after it was drawn. A few hours later the patient's test results are as follows:
 (1)Hepatitis A IgM antibodies (IgM anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (2)Hepatitis A antibodies (anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (3)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) "Negative"
 (4)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) quantitative 0.40 IU/mL (reference range: &lt;0.50 IU/mL)
 (5)Hepatitis B virus e antibodies (anti-HBVe) "Negative"
 (6)Hepatitis B surface antigen (HBVsAg) "Negative"
 (7)Hepatitis B surface antibody (anti-HBVs) "Negative"
 (8)Hepatitis C antibody screen (anti-HCV) "Positive"
 (9)Hepatitis C antibodies Signal to Cut-off Ratio 10.8 s/co (reference range: 0.0-0.9 s/co)

Per CDC recommendations, a confirmatory Hepatitis C RNA PCR test is performed because of the positive Anti-HCV findings. The next day, the Hepatitis C RNA PCR test results confirm the patient is positive for hepatitis, with a value of 761120 IU/ml (reference range: &lt; 43). The Hepatitis C results trigger an Abnormal Flag or "High", as well as the comment:
 "Negative: &lt; 0.8, Indeterminate 0.8 - 0.9, Positive: &gt; 0.9. In order to reduce the incidence of a false positive result, the CDC recommends that all s/co ratios between 1.0 and 10.9 be confirmed with additional Verification or PCR testing."
The final report is completed on that day and sent to the ordering provider.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and LRI_5.0_1.1-GU_FRU  message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to import and incorporate Parent-Child Reflex results.
Tests support for multiple comments for one test result.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Proper display of the results (OBX-5) with structured numeric format (#4 and 9) with interpretations (OBX-8) 
Comments for result of the lab result identified as "Hepatitis C virus Ab Signal/Cutoff in Serum or Plasma by Immunoassay" is properly grouped with its result.
Results for the Reflex test are properly associated with the result that spawned its creation, which is the detection of Hepatitis C virus Antibody in Serum, as part of the Hepatitis A B C Panel screen.
</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the reflex message.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Parent child(FRN)-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Parent child(FRN) Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.   This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process reflex test reports which use the parent/child reporting structure.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a reflex result message when the filler order number does not uniquely identifies the test ordered. (FRN profiles).</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_5.1_1.1-GU_FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex" version="20160218">
		<Description>A patient is hospitalized for substance abuse. The physician orders a hepatitis panel through the hospital's EHR system to test for Hepatitis A, B and C antibodies/antigens. The serum specimen is collected the same day at in the morning and submitted to the hospital lab for testing via their LIS right after it was drawn. A few hours later the patient's test results are as follows:
 (1)Hepatitis A IgM antibodies (IgM anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (2)Hepatitis A antibodies (anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (3)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) "Negative"
 (4)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) quantitative 0.40 IU/mL (reference range: &lt;0.50 IU/mL)
 (5)Hepatitis B virus e antibodies (anti-HBVe) "Negative"
 (6)Hepatitis B surface antigen (HBVsAg) "Negative"
 (7)Hepatitis B surface antibody (anti-HBVs) "Negative"
 (8)Hepatitis C antibody screen (anti-HCV) "Positive"
 (9)Hepatitis C antibodies Signal to Cut-off Ratio 10.8 s/co (reference range: 0.0-0.9 s/co)
The hospital LIS sends an LRI message containing these results to the EHR-S. </Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability to import and incorporate a typically populated Hepatitis Panel lab result message.
Tests support for multiple comments for one test result.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Proper display of the results (OBX-5) with structured numeric format (#4 and 9) with interpretations (OBX-8) 
Comments for result of the lab result identified as "Hepatitis C virus Ab Signal/Cutoff in Serum or Plasma by Immunoassay" is properly grouped with its result.
Results for the Reflex test are properly associated with the result that spawned its creation, which is the detection of Hepatitis C virus Antibody in Serum, as part of the Hepatitis A B C Panel screen.
</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the parent message.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_5.1_2.1-GU-FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex" version="20160218">
		<Description>A patient is hospitalized for substance abuse. The physician orders a hepatitis panel through the hospital's EHR system to test for Hepatitis A, B and C antibodies/antigens. The serum specimen is collected the same day at in the morning and submitted to the hospital lab for testing via their LIS right after it was drawn. A few hours later the patient's test results are as follows:
 (1)Hepatitis A IgM antibodies (IgM anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (2)Hepatitis A antibodies (anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (3)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) "Negative"
 (4)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) quantitative 0.40 IU/mL (reference range: &lt;0.50 IU/mL)
 (5)Hepatitis B virus e antibodies (anti-HBVe) "Negative"
 (6)Hepatitis B surface antigen (HBVsAg) "Negative"
 (7)Hepatitis B surface antibody (anti-HBVs) "Negative"
 (8)Hepatitis C antibody screen (anti-HCV) "Positive"
 (9)Hepatitis C antibodies Signal to Cut-off Ratio 10.8 s/co (reference range: 0.0-0.9 s/co)

Per CDC recommendations, a confirmatory Hepatitis C RNA PCR test is performed because of the positive Anti-HCV findings. The next day, the Hepatitis C RNA PCR test results confirm the patient is positive for hepatitis, with a value of 761120 IU/ml (reference range: &lt; 43). The Hepatitis C results trigger an Abnormal Flag or "High", as well as the comment:
 "Negative: &lt; 0.8, Indeterminate 0.8 - 0.9, Positive: &gt; 0.9. In order to reduce the incidence of a false positive result, the CDC recommends that all s/co ratios between 1.0 and 10.9 be confirmed with additional Verification or PCR testing."
The final report is completed on that day and sent to the ordering provider.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test Case LRI_5.0_1.1-GU_FRN  message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to import and incorporate Parent-Child Reflex results.
Tests support for multiple comments for one test result.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Proper display of the results (OBX-5) with structured numeric format (#4 and 9) with interpretations (OBX-8) 
Comments for result of the lab result identified as "Hepatitis C virus Ab Signal/Cutoff in Serum or Plasma by Immunoassay" is properly grouped with its result.
Results for the Reflex test are properly associated with the result that spawned its creation, which is the detection of Hepatitis C virus Antibody in Serum, as part of the Hepatitis A B C Panel screen.
</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the reflex message.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Pap Smear-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="Pap Smear Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.    This test plan is designed to test the system' capability to process a simple anatomic pathology report containing "Ask at Order Entry Questions (AOEs)".</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_6.0_1.1-GU" date="2/18/2016" name="final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mrs. Delores Lopez is a 30 year old Hispanic female who presents to Dr. Radon's clinic for a routine gynecological examination. A pap smear sample is collected after confirming with Ms. Lopez that her last menstrual period was two weeks ago.  A pap smear is ordered from Century Hospital's clinical lab through the Clinic's EHR and the specimen is sent to the lab for testing along with the response to the ask on order (AOE) question "Date of last menstrual period". Century Hospital's clinical lab forwarded this order to Pacific Anatomic Pathology Services which performed the test. 
The final results were sent from Century Hospital's clinical lab's LIS to the Provider's EHR.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid typically populated message for anatomic pathology report for a PAP smear.
Demonstrate ability to support Ask at Order Entry Questions.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Answers for Ask at Order Entry questions (OBX-5) are distinguished from the results for the same order.
Notes are related to the coded result of the Pap report
Display of pdf document sent this message.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case  is evaluating the handling of an Anatomic Pathology report, including sending a pdf, and Ask at Order Questions responses.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="NG" date="2/18/2016" name="NG" version="20160218">
		<Comments>This is the Non-Globally Unique Profile Component (NG) test case group - identifiers in these test cases may use OIDs, other identifiers or just the namespaceID to identify the assigning authority.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="PT and INR -NG" date="2/18/2016" name="PT and INR Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers a simple electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  The EHR-S receives and incorporates the messages, and creates and sends an acknowledgement message.  The LIS system receives the acknowledgement message.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate capability to support minimally populated messages (single occurrences of all required ("R") elements).</TestObjectives>
		<Comments>The initial test plan is a "smoke test" to reveal simple failures  severe enough to preclude further testing.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_0.0_1.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Smoke test" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. Hector Ramos is a 81 year old Hispanic male who is on warfarin therapy.  Mr. Ramos presents to  Good Health Clinic to see Dr. Radon for a routine check up.   The doctor orders a Prothrombin Time (PT + INR) test from the clinical lab at Century Hospital using the clinic's EHR system and instruct Mr. Ramos to go to the laboratory's patient service center to have the blood sample collected.   The laboratory performs the requested test and the final result was  10.5  sec with a ref range of 9.5-13.8 sec  and the INR calculated to be 1.0    {INR}   with a  normal reference range being 0.8 and 1.2 {INR}.  The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the Good health Clinic's EHR system.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Minimally populated message.
Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate all required data elements for the test case:
Minimally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSH segment.
Minimally populated PID Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the PID segment.
Minimally populated ORC Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the ORC segment.
Minimally populated OBR Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the OBR segment.
Minimally populated OBX Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the OBX segment.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>No Notes.</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the "smoke test" - testing basic functionality and support for all Required elements per the LRI IG to reveal simple failures severe enough to preclude further testing..</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="ACK_0.0_3.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Smoke test ACK" version="20160218">
		<Description>Dr Radon's EHR-S transmits an accept acknowledgement message to Century Hospital's LIS which indicates the ORU message Prothrombin Time (PT + INR) test results has been successfully received.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>No Post-Condition.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Minimally populated message.
Demonstrate capability to support creating a positive accept acknowledgment Message in response to successful receipt of the ORU message:
Minimally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSH segment.
Minimally populated MSA Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSA segment.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>No Notes.</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the initial "smoke testing" to reveal simple failures of the acknowledgment message severe enough to preclude further testing.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="ACK_0.0_4.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Smoke test App ACK" version="20160218">
		<Description>Dr Radon's EHR-S  transmits an application acknowledgement message to Century Hospital's LIS which indicates the ORU message Prothrombin Time (PT + INR) test results has been successfully parsed and incorporated.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>Test message for ACK_0.0_5.1-NG will be created.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Minimally populated message.
Demonstrate capability to support creating a positive application acknowledgment Message in response to successful receipt of the ORU message:
Minimally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSH segment.
Minimally populated MSA Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSA segment.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>No Notes.</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the initial "smoke testing" to reveal simple failures of the application acknowledgment message severe enough to preclude further testing.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="ACK_0.0_5.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Smoke test ACK to AppACK" version="20160218">
		<Description>Century Hospital's LIS transmits an accept acknowledgement message to Dr Radon's EHR-S which indicates the Application Acknowledgement message has been successfully received.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>No Post-Condition.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Minimally populated message.
Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate all required data elements for the accept acknowledgement test case:
Minimally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSH segment.
Minimally populated MSA Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSA segment.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>To support real-time dynamic testing, the Tester at their discretion, may selectively modify result acknowledgement data prior to importing the test message into the EHR technology.</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the initial "smoke testing" to reveal simple failures of the acknowledgment message severe enough to preclude further testing.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Sed Rate-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Sed Rate" version="20160218">
		<Description>These test plans are designed to test capability to process maximally populated message (all the R, RE, C(a/b) elements defined in the implementation guide), the progression from a 'final' to 'corrected' report, and to report the test was not performed due to a specimen quality issue.</Description>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to corrected-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to corrected header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  The EHR-S receives and incorporates  the message.   These test plans are designed to test capability to process maximally populated message (all the elements defined in the implementation guide)  as well as the progression from a "final" to "corrected" report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate capability to support maximally populated messages - all supported (R,RE,C(a/b)) elements including multiple occurrences of repeating elements.
Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final and  corrected results message.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_1.0_1.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with pain, swelling, and redness in several joints including his elbows, wrists, knees, and hips. In order to screen for rheumatoid diseases, Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered an erythrocyte sedimentation rate (ESR or Sed Rate) blood test using the Good Health Clinic's EHR system,  specifying that the laboratory's patient service center was to draw the blood specimen from the patient later that same day.  Dr Radon also requests that the results be CC'd to Dr Pafford M. Hamlin Sr, a specialist to which he is referring Mr. Jones as well as Dr. Daniel Davison who is Mr. Jones' regular doctor.
The laboratory performs the requested test and the final result was 10 mm/hr, a normal value with the normal reference range being 0-17 mm/hr. The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the Good health Clinic's EHR system used in Dr. Radon's office practice on the same day.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Maximally populated message.
Demonstrate ability to  import and incorporate all supported relevant (R,RE,C(a/b)) data elements for the test case, including multiple occurrences:
Demonstrate the capability to support Timing_Qty Group and Timing/Quantity Segment (TQ1).
Demonstrate the capability to support Notes and Comments Segments (NTE) that follow the Observation Request Segment (OBR), including multiple occurrences.
Maximally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the MSH segment.
Maximally populated PID Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the PID segment. 
Maximally populated NTE segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including proper handling of formatted text.
Maximally populated ORC Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the ORC segment.
Maximally populated OBR Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the OBR segment. 
Maximally populated SPM Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements in the SPM segment. 
Maximally populated TQ1 Segment - Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to support all supported data elements including repeating elements in the TQ1 segment .
Specific test points include the use of the NM data type for OBX.2, the value of "10" for results (OBX.5), the value of "N" for abnormal flags (OBX.8), and the observation results status is "F" (OBX.11).</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>In addition to the review of all elements, check that the Notes after the order are properly formatted and displayed.</Notes>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_1.0_2.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="corrected" version="20160218">
		<Description>Based on LRI_1.0_Sed_Rate and LRI_1.1_Sed_Rate:
Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with pain, swelling, and redness in several joints including his elbows, wrists, knees, and hips. In order to rule out rheumatoid arthritis, Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered an erythrocyte sedimentation rate (ESR or Sed Rate) blood test to be performed, specifying that the laboratory was to draw the blood specimen from the patient the same day. The final result of this test was 10 mm/hr, a normal value with the normal reference range being 0-17 mm/hr. The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice later that same day.

The ESR test instrument was recalibrated and the ESR specimen was re-analyzed. After the recalibration and re-analysis, the result value for Mr. Jones' ESR test changed from 10 mm/hr to 20 mm/hr. A Corrected result report with a result value of 20 mm/hr and an abnormal flag of "H" was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and LRI_1.0_1.1-NG has been previously received by the EHR-S and incorporated with the patient's record.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the ability to update the patient record based on corrected results.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_1.0-GU_Sed_Rate_Final test case prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status – now C instead of F (OBR-25)
Result date/time is later than before (OBR-22)
Result for Sed Rate changed from 10 to 20 (OBX-5), which changed the interpretation (OBX-8) from N to H and result status (OBX-11) is C
An additional comment (NTE after OBX) is displayed at the result level, indicating: "Specimen re-analyzed per request of ordering provider."</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11 for a corrected result.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Specimen rejected-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Specimen rejected header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  The EHR system receives and incorporates an electronic lab result message.    This test plan is designed to test capability to process a report in which a test was not performed due to a specimen quality issue.</Description>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate capability to report the test was not performed due to a specimen quality issue.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_1.2_1.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="specimen rejection" version="20160218">
		<Description>Ms. Janet Anderson is a 26 year old white female who presented with fever of unknown origin and generalized joint pain. In order to rule out infection and autoimmune disease, Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered an erythrocyte sedimentation rate (ESR or Sed Rate) blood test to be performed. A blood specimen for the ESR test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab for processing. The analysis could not be performed because the specimen arrived clotted. No result value could be obtained. A Specimen Rejection message for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to import and incorporate a valid Rejected Specimen message.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Since the specimen was rejected there is no lab result in the Juror Document; there is however specimen reject information that needs to be displayed.
This test case requires display verification only. 
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status (OBR-25) is X 
Information about the specimen condition (SPM-24) and reject reason (SPM-21)
A result value (OBX-5) showing that the test could not be performed with attached comment (NTE after OBX) as explanation.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case tests handling of specimen rejection.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="CBC-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="CBC header" version="20160218">
		<Description>These test plans are designed to test capability to process  the progression from a 'partial' to 'final'  report, from a 'final'  to 'wrong patient' report, as well as from a 'final'  to 'amended' report.</Description>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Partial result to final-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Partial result to final header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.    This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process the progression from a "partial" to "final" report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a partial and final results message.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_2.0_0.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="partial" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a history of fever, fatigue, and shortness of breath on exertion. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a complete blood count (CBC) test to be performed. A blood specimen for the CBC test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The laboratory director at this hospital is Dr. Phil J. Knowsalot, III. The blood specimen was analyzed, and before all of the results are available a partial report is generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to Dr. Hamlin Pafford.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to import and incorporate a valid LRI CBC panel result that contains some, but not all of the result values for the expected OBX segments.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only.</Notes>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_2.0_1.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a history of fever, fatigue, and shortness of breath on exertion. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a complete blood count (CBC) test to be performed. A blood specimen for the CBC test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The laboratory director at this hospital is Dr. Phil J. Knowsalot, III. The blood specimen was analyzed, and before all of the results are available a partial report is generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to  Dr. Hamlin Pafford.

The next day the all results of the CBC test are available and a final report is generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to Dr. Hamlin Pafford.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test Case LRI_2.0_0.1-NG message has  been received and incorporated into the EHR-S.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to update the patient record based on additional results received in the report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_2.0_0.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from A to F
The 9 previously empty results now have results (OBX-5), interpretations (OBX-8) and status (OBX-11) has changed from I to F</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to wrong patient-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to wrong patient header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process the progression from a "final" to "wrong patient" report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final result message and handle report that the initial final result was sent for the wrong patient.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_2.1_1.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="final_Wrong" version="20160218">
		<Description>The laboratory at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA 90067 received a blood specimen from Dr. Radon's office on patient Willow A. Jones for a complete blood count (CBC) test.  The patient was identified in the system as a 14 year old white female.  The blood specimen was analyzed and the final result revealed critically high WBC of 32,000/uL.   Dr. Radon was notified of the critical result by phone and the laboratory included the following comment in the report , "Critically high WBC reported to Dr. Radon by phone the day of the report." The final test result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to import and incorporate a final valid LRI CBC panel result message</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_2.1_2.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Corrected_Wrong" version="20160218">
		<Description>The laboratory at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA 90067 received a blood specimen from Dr. Radon's office on patient Willow A. Jones for a complete blood count (CBC) test.  The patient was identified in the system as a 14 year old white female.  The blood specimen was analyzed and the final result revealed critically high WBC of 32,000/uL.   Dr. Radon was notified of the critical result by phone and the laboratory included the following comment in the report , "Critically high WBC reported to Dr. Radon by phone the day of the report." The final test result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office.

The following morning, Dr. Radon upon review of results noticed several anomalies with the results and notified the lab. The lab traced the issue back to mislabeled specimens and reissued the report as corrected, indicating that the results were reported on the wrong patient.  The laboratory included a comment, stating, "All results previously reported for this patient were reported in error; they do not apply to this patient."</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_2.1_1.1-NG message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to update the patient record when corrected results indicate the prior results were for the wrong patient.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_2.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C
An additional comment (NTE after OBR) is displayed under the Order
All result values (OBX-5) are “”, without interpretation (OBX-8) and Result Status (OBX-11) has changed from F to W</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11 and the proper handling of OBX-5 values when indicating the prior results were reported for the wrong patient.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to Amended-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to Amended header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.    This test plan is designed to test the EHR-S' capability to process the progression from a "final" to "amended" report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final and amended results message.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Use of the amended result status code 'A" is permitted, so this test case constitutes an optional test case, should partners agree to support this concept.</Notes>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_3.1_1.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="final_amended" version="20160218">
		<Description>The laboratory at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA 90067 received a blood specimen from Dr. Radon's office on patient Willow C. Jones for a complete blood count (CBC) test.  The patient was identified in the system as a 14 year old white female.  The blood specimen was analyzed and the final result revealed high WBC, particularly Lymphocytes and Neutrophils as well as high hematocrit, MCV and MCH. The final test result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office. </Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to import and incorporate a final valid LRI CBC panel result message</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_3.1_2.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Corrected_Amended" version="20160218">
		<Description>The laboratory at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA 90067 received a blood specimen from Dr. Radon's office on patient Willow C. Jones for a complete blood count (CBC) test.  The patient was identified in the system as a 14 year old white female.  The blood specimen was analyzed and the final result revealed high WBC, particularly Lymphocytes and Neutrophils as well as high hematocrit, MCV and MCH. The final test result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office.

The following morning, Dr. Radon upon review of results noticed that the Willow's Date of birth was listed as 12/27/2001, but Willow is only 4 years old, not 14. Dr. Radon notified the lab to correct the Date of Birth to 12/27/2010. The lab reviewed the results and adjusts the normal ranges for the observations based on on the updated age from adult reference ranges to 4 year old and re-issued the report as amended, leaving only the elevated WBC, with increased Neutrophils and a low hemoglobin as abnormal results.  The laboratory included a comment, stating, "The patient's DOB was corrected by request of the ordering provider. The normal ranges are based on age group and so were adjusted accordingly for most of these observations, which led to a change in interpretations of existing results. Please review all interpretations in detail."</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_3.1_1.1-NG message has previously been sent.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to update the patient record when interpretations and reference ranges were changed due to demographic information updates in an amended report.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_2.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas: 
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C
An additional comment (NTE after OBR) is displayed under the Order
No change to Result value (OBX-5), but changes to Reference Ranges (OBX-7) in most cases,  interpretation (OBX-8) in some (hemoglobin, hematocrit, MCV, MCH, Lymphocytes) and Result Status (OBX-11) has changed from F to A, where changes have occurred.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11for results in an amended report.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Lipid Panel-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Lipid Panel Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.  These test plan are designed to test the system's capability to process reports containing "Ask at Order Entry Questions (AOEs)" and handle receipt of duplicate messages.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a message that contains an Ask at Order Entry Questions (AOEs) and to demonstrate the proper handling of receipt of duplicate reports.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_3.0_1.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="initial result - final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented for a cardiology exam. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a lipid panel test to be performed to check for hyperlipidemia. A blood specimen for the lipid panel test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The laboratory director at this hospital is Dr. Phil J. Knowsalot, III. The blood specimen was analyzed, and the final result of the lipid panel test showed that all components were within the normal range. The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to Dr. Pafford M. Hamlin, Sr.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR to import and incorporate a valid LRI message for a lipid panel blood test lab result.
Demonstrate ability to support Ask at Order Entry Questions.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only. 
Concentrate on the following areas:  
Answers for Ask at Order Entry questions (OBX-5) are distinguished from the results for the same order.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the handling of Ask at Order Entry questions as part of a typical Lipid Panel.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_3.0_2.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="duplicates" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented for a cardiology exam. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a lipid panel test to be performed to check for hyperlipidemia. A blood specimen for the lipid panel test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The laboratory director at this hospital is Dr. Phil J. Knowsalot, III. The blood specimen was analyzed, and the final result of the lipid panel test showed that all components were within the normal range. The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice. A copy of the test result report was sent to Dr. Pafford M. Hamlin, Sr.

A duplicate report of the report is sent shortly after the first.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_3.0_1.1-NG message has been received and incorporated into the EHR-S.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the proper handling of receipt of duplicate reports.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_3.0_1.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only and is testing how the EHR-S behaves when it gets the exact same report.

</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the handling of duplicate reports based on OBR-22 comparison.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Culture and Suscep-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Culture and Suscep Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>These test plans are designed to test capability to process the progression from a 'preliminary' to 'final' to 'corrected' microbiology report.</Description>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a preliminary, final, and corrected result microbiology message.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Preliminary result-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Preliminary result Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S. This test plan tests the systems' capability to process  a "preliminary" microbiology Culture and Sensitivity report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a preliminary result microbiology message.</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.0_1.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="preliminary result" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing.  The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the EHR-S can correctly incorporate a valid typically populated message for a preliminary Stool Culture microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Result Report Status (OBR-25) is P 
3 different results (OBX-5) and their interpretations (OBX-8) for the same test are properly displayed with a Result Status (OBX-11) of P</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to corrected (FRU)-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to corrected (FRU) Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The EHR system receives and incorporates an electronic lab result message.    This test plan and the previous test plan are designed to test the EHR-S' capability to process the progression from a "preliminary" to "final" to "corrected" microbiology Culture and Sensitivity reports.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final and corrected result microbiology message when the filler order number uniquely identifies the test ordered. (FRU profiles).</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.1_2.1-NG_FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="prelim to final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing.  The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-NG message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for a final Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from P to F
3 different results (OBX-5) and their interpretations (OBX-8) for the same test are properly displayed; Result Status (OBX-11) changed from P to F
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.
</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.1_3.1-NG_FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="final to corrected" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.

Five hours later the laboratorian realizes that the result in the susceptibility suite for Shigella Flexneri was wrong and corrects the report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-NG AND LRI_4.1_2.1-NG_FRU messages have been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for a corrected Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU and LRI_4.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).
For the susceptibility test on Shigella flexneri the Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C - ensure the related results show:
For the test identified as "Ampicillin" the result (OBX-5) changed from 16ug/mL to 32ug/mL and interpretation (OBX-8) from "I" to "R" and the Result Status (OBX-11) changed from F to C.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.1_4.1-NG_FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="final to corrected/Appended" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.

Five hours later the laboratorian realizes that the result in the susceptibility suite for Shigella Flexneri were missing results for additional antibiotic.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-NG AND LRI_4.1_2.1-NG_FRU messages have been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for an appended Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU and LRI_4.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).
For the susceptibility test on Shigella flexneri the Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C - ensure the related results show:
additional tests have been appended, i.e. are new: 
Result (OBX-5) and interpretation (OBX-8) for "Trimethoprim+Sulfamethoxazole" and "Ciprofloxacin".</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Final result to corrected (FRN)-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Final result to corrected (FRN) Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The EHR system receives and incorporates an electronic lab result message.    This test plan and the previous test plan are designed to test the EHR-S' capability to process the progression from a "preliminary" to "final" to "corrected" microbiology Culture and Sensitivity reports.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a final and corrected result microbiology message when the filler order number does not uniquely identifies the test ordered. (FRN profiles).</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.2_2.1-NG_FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="prelim to final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing.  The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-NG message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for a final Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from P to F
3 different results (OBX-5) and their interpretations (OBX-8) for the same test are properly displayed; Result Status (OBX-11) changed from P to F
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.
</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.2_3.1-NG_FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="final to corrected" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.

Five hours later the laboratorian realizes that the result in the susceptibility suite for Shigella Flexneri was wrong and corrects the report.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-NG AND LRI_4.2_2.1-NG_FRN messages have been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for a corrected Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU and LRI_4.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).
For the susceptibility test on Shigella flexneri the Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C - ensure the related results show:
For the test identified as "Ampicillin" the result (OBX-5) changed from 16ug/mL to 32ug/mL and interpretation (OBX-8) from "I" to "R" and the Result Status (OBX-11) changed from F to C.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_4.2_4.1-NG_FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="final to corrected/Appended" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mr. William A. Jones is a 51 year old white male who presented with a complaint of diarrhea times 3 days. Dr. Nicholas Radon ordered a stool culture test to be performed. A stool specimen for the microbiology test was collected from the patient and sent to the clinical lab at Century Hospital, 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, for processing. The stool specimen was analyzed and preliminary result are sent 24 hours later, identifying E. coli O157:H7, Salmonella and Shigella flexneri.

Approximately 48 hours later the Final results, including susceptibility testing of Shigella flexneri are available. The final result report was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the ambulatory EHR used in Dr. Radon's office practice.

Five hours later the laboratorian realizes that the result in the susceptibility suite for Shigella Flexneri were missing results for additional antibiotic.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and Test case LRI_4.0_1.1-NG AND LRI_4.2_2.1-NG_FRN messages have been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid Parent-Child message for an appended Stool Culture/Susceptibility microbiology test report.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>Run LRI_4.0_1.1-GU and LRI_4.0_2.1-GU prior to this test case. This test case requires display verification only.
Concentrate on the following areas:
Check that the parent-child linkage is correctly implemented:
The susceptibility test results are linked to the correct result that spawned the respective susceptibility testing, e.g. once for "Salmonella I, group O:4" and once for "Shigella flexneri", both results of the same parent order (Stool culture).
For the susceptibility test on Shigella flexneri the Result Report Status (OBR-25) changed from F to C - ensure the related results show:
additional tests have been appended, i.e. are new: 
Result (OBX-5) and interpretation (OBX-8) for "Trimethoprim+Sulfamethoxazole" and "Ciprofloxacin".</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case is evaluating the proper use of OBR-22 to establish chronological order of reports and correct use of the status codes in OBR-25 and OBX-11.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Reflex Hepatitis-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex Hepatitis header" version="20160218">
		<Description>This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process reflex test reports which use the parent/child reporting structure.</Description>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Parent child(FRU)-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Parent child(FRU) Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.   This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process reflex test reports which use the parent/child reporting structure.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a reflex result message when the filler order number uniquely identifies the test ordered. (FRU profiles).</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_5.0_1.1-NG_FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex" version="20160218">
		<Description>A patient is hospitalized for substance abuse. The physician orders a hepatitis panel through the hospital's EHR system to test for Hepatitis A, B and C antibodies/antigens. The serum specimen is collected the same day at in the morning and submitted to the hospital lab for testing via their LIS right after it was drawn. A few hours later the patient's test results are as follows:
 (1)Hepatitis A IgM antibodies (IgM anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (2)Hepatitis A antibodies (anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (3)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) "Negative"
 (4)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) quantitative 0.40 IU/mL (reference range: &lt;0.50 IU/mL)
 (5)Hepatitis B virus e antibodies (anti-HBVe) "Negative"
 (6)Hepatitis B surface antigen (HBVsAg) "Negative"
 (7)Hepatitis B surface antibody (anti-HBVs) "Negative"
 (8)Hepatitis C antibody screen (anti-HCV) "Positive"
 (9)Hepatitis C antibodies Signal to Cut-off Ratio 10.8 s/co (reference range: 0.0-0.9 s/co)
The hospital LIS sends an LRI message containing these results to the EHR-S. </Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability to import and incorporate a typically populated Hepatitis Panel lab result message.
Tests support for multiple comments for one test result.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Proper display of the results (OBX-5) with structured numeric format (#4 and 9) with interpretations (OBX-8) 
Comments for result of the lab result identified as "Hepatitis C virus Ab Signal/Cutoff in Serum or Plasma by Immunoassay" is properly grouped with its result.
Results for the Reflex test are properly associated with the result that spawned its creation, which is the detection of Hepatitis C virus Antibody in Serum, as part of the Hepatitis A B C Panel screen.
</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the parent message.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_5.0_2.1-NG-FRU" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex" version="20160218">
		<Description>A patient is hospitalized for substance abuse. The physician orders a hepatitis panel through the hospital's EHR system to test for Hepatitis A, B and C antibodies/antigens. The serum specimen is collected the same day at in the morning and submitted to the hospital lab for testing via their LIS right after it was drawn. A few hours later the patient's test results are as follows:
 (1)Hepatitis A IgM antibodies (IgM anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (2)Hepatitis A antibodies (anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (3)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) "Negative"
 (4)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) quantitative 0.40 IU/mL (reference range: &lt;0.50 IU/mL)
 (5)Hepatitis B virus e antibodies (anti-HBVe) "Negative"
 (6)Hepatitis B surface antigen (HBVsAg) "Negative"
 (7)Hepatitis B surface antibody (anti-HBVs) "Negative"
 (8)Hepatitis C antibody screen (anti-HCV) "Positive"
 (9)Hepatitis C antibodies Signal to Cut-off Ratio 10.8 s/co (reference range: 0.0-0.9 s/co)

Per CDC recommendations, a confirmatory Hepatitis C RNA PCR test is performed because of the positive Anti-HCV findings. The next day, the Hepatitis C RNA PCR test results confirm the patient is positive for hepatitis, with a value of 761120 IU/ml (reference range: &lt; 43). The Hepatitis C results trigger an Abnormal Flag or "High", as well as the comment:
 "Negative: &lt; 0.8, Indeterminate 0.8 - 0.9, Positive: &gt; 0.9. In order to reduce the incidence of a false positive result, the CDC recommends that all s/co ratios between 1.0 and 10.9 be confirmed with additional Verification or PCR testing."
The final report is completed on that day and sent to the ordering provider.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and LRI_5.0_1.1-GU_FRU  message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to import and incorporate Parent-Child Reflex results.
Tests support for multiple comments for one test result.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Proper display of the results (OBX-5) with structured numeric format (#4 and 9) with interpretations (OBX-8) 
Comments for result of the lab result identified as "Hepatitis C virus Ab Signal/Cutoff in Serum or Plasma by Immunoassay" is properly grouped with its result.
Results for the Reflex test are properly associated with the result that spawned its creation, which is the detection of Hepatitis C virus Antibody in Serum, as part of the Hepatitis A B C Panel screen.
</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the reflex message.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Parent child(FRN)-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Parent child(FRN) Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.   This test plan is designed to test the systems' capability to process reflex test reports which use the parent/child reporting structure.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate ability to import and incorporate a reflex result message when the filler order number does not uniquely identifies the test ordered. (FRN profiles).</TestObjectives>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_5.1_1.1-NG_FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex" version="20160218">
		<Description>A patient is hospitalized for substance abuse. The physician orders a hepatitis panel through the hospital's EHR system to test for Hepatitis A, B and C antibodies/antigens. The serum specimen is collected the same day at in the morning and submitted to the hospital lab for testing via their LIS right after it was drawn. A few hours later the patient's test results are as follows:
 (1)Hepatitis A IgM antibodies (IgM anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (2)Hepatitis A antibodies (anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (3)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) "Negative"
 (4)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) quantitative 0.40 IU/mL (reference range: &lt;0.50 IU/mL)
 (5)Hepatitis B virus e antibodies (anti-HBVe) "Negative"
 (6)Hepatitis B surface antigen (HBVsAg) "Negative"
 (7)Hepatitis B surface antibody (anti-HBVs) "Negative"
 (8)Hepatitis C antibody screen (anti-HCV) "Positive"
 (9)Hepatitis C antibodies Signal to Cut-off Ratio 10.8 s/co (reference range: 0.0-0.9 s/co)
The hospital LIS sends an LRI message containing these results to the EHR-S. </Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability to import and incorporate a typically populated Hepatitis Panel lab result message.
Tests support for multiple comments for one test result.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Proper display of the results (OBX-5) with structured numeric format (#4 and 9) with interpretations (OBX-8) 
Comments for result of the lab result identified as "Hepatitis C virus Ab Signal/Cutoff in Serum or Plasma by Immunoassay" is properly grouped with its result.
Results for the Reflex test are properly associated with the result that spawned its creation, which is the detection of Hepatitis C virus Antibody in Serum, as part of the Hepatitis A B C Panel screen.
</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the parent message.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_5.1_2.1-NG-FRN" date="2/18/2016" name="Reflex" version="20160218">
		<Description>A patient is hospitalized for substance abuse. The physician orders a hepatitis panel through the hospital's EHR system to test for Hepatitis A, B and C antibodies/antigens. The serum specimen is collected the same day at in the morning and submitted to the hospital lab for testing via their LIS right after it was drawn. A few hours later the patient's test results are as follows:
 (1)Hepatitis A IgM antibodies (IgM anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (2)Hepatitis A antibodies (anti-HAV) "Negative"
 (3)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) "Negative"
 (4)Hepatitis B core antibodies (anti-HBVc) quantitative 0.40 IU/mL (reference range: &lt;0.50 IU/mL)
 (5)Hepatitis B virus e antibodies (anti-HBVe) "Negative"
 (6)Hepatitis B surface antigen (HBVsAg) "Negative"
 (7)Hepatitis B surface antibody (anti-HBVs) "Negative"
 (8)Hepatitis C antibody screen (anti-HCV) "Positive"
 (9)Hepatitis C antibodies Signal to Cut-off Ratio 10.8 s/co (reference range: 0.0-0.9 s/co)

Per CDC recommendations, a confirmatory Hepatitis C RNA PCR test is performed because of the positive Anti-HCV findings. The next day, the Hepatitis C RNA PCR test results confirm the patient is positive for hepatitis, with a value of 761120 IU/ml (reference range: &lt; 43). The Hepatitis C results trigger an Abnormal Flag or "High", as well as the comment:
 "Negative: &lt; 0.8, Indeterminate 0.8 - 0.9, Positive: &gt; 0.9. In order to reduce the incidence of a false positive result, the CDC recommends that all s/co ratios between 1.0 and 10.9 be confirmed with additional Verification or PCR testing."
The final report is completed on that day and sent to the ordering provider.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
and LRI_5.1_1.1-NG_FRN  message has been received and incorporated.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate the capability of the EHR-S to import and incorporate Parent-Child Reflex results.
Tests support for multiple comments for one test result.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Proper display of the results (OBX-5) with structured numeric format (#4 and 9) with interpretations (OBX-8) 
Comments for result of the lab result identified as "Hepatitis C virus Ab Signal/Cutoff in Serum or Plasma by Immunoassay" is properly grouped with its result.
Results for the Reflex test are properly associated with the result that spawned its creation, which is the detection of Hepatitis C virus Antibody in Serum, as part of the Hepatitis A B C Panel screen.
</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the reflex message.
Special case test aspects include ensuring that the system can correctly process the data elements for linking parent/child results in accordance with the requirements specified in the implementation guide for the FRN and FRU profiles.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="Pap Smear-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="Pap Smear Header" version="20160218">
		<Description>The LIS system creates and delivers an electronic lab result message to the EHR-S.    This test plan is designed to test the system' capability to process a simple anatomic pathology report containing "Ask at Order Entry Questions (AOEs)".</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
	<TestCaseMetaData id="LRI_6.0_1.1-NG" date="2/18/2016" name="final" version="20160218">
		<Description>Mrs. Delores Lopez is a 30 year old Hispanic female who presents to Dr. Radon's clinic for a routine gynecological examination. A pap smear sample is collected after confirming with Ms. Lopez that her last menstrual period was two weeks ago.  A pap smear is ordered from Century Hospital's clinical lab through the Clinic's EHR and the specimen is sent to the lab for testing along with the response to the ask on order (AOE) question "Date of last menstrual period". Century Hospital's clinical lab forwarded this order to Pacific Anatomic Pathology Services which performed the test. 
The final results were sent from Century Hospital's clinical lab's LIS to the Provider's EHR.</Description>
		<PreCondition>Patient information is pre-loaded in the EHR-S.
No other Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>The test message information received by the EHR-S has been incorporated with the patient's record.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Determine if the system can correctly import and incorporate a valid typically populated message for anatomic pathology report for a PAP smear.
Demonstrate ability to support Ask at Order Entry Questions.
</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>For display verification focus on these areas:
Answers for Ask at Order Entry questions (OBX-5) are distinguished from the results for the same order.
Notes are related to the coded result of the Pap report
Display of pdf document sent this message.</Notes>
		<Comments>This test case  is evaluating the handling of an Anatomic Pathology report, including sending a pdf, and Ask at Order Questions responses.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>
</TestCases>