<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ASCII" standalone="no"?>
<TestCaseMetaData date="2014-12-10 23:28:14" id="1" name="EDOS_1.0_3.1-M04_NG_M04_New" version="1">
    <Description>The originator of the eDOS is the Century Hospital Clinical Laboratory located at 2070 Test Park, Los Angeles, CA, 90067, CLIA: 24D9871327 , phone number: (310) 461-3666.&#13;
The Sender is the  Century Hospital Clinical Laboratory LIS.&#13;
The Receiver is Dr. Radon's Office EHR.&#13;
&#13;
The initial Laboratory Test Compendium build from Century Hospital Clinical Laboratory is a subset of their Directory of Services.  It based upon the most commonly ordered lab tests by Dr. Radon.  This compendium is delivered electronically to Dr. Nicholas Radon's practice EHR, as agreed to between Laboratory and Dr. Radon's Office and EHR Vendor.   The EHR will integrate the eDOS into its test directory and use it to allow Dr. Radon to place orders electronically to Century Hospital's Clinical Laboratory.   The initial laboratory test compendium is composed of three messages.  After Century Hospital's LIS successfully transmits the first and second messages which provides information about each individual observation and each orderable battery or profile,  it sends the third message which provides information about CPT procedure codes for each orderable panel and individual observation.</Description>
    <PreCondition>EDOS_1.0_1.1-M08_New&#13;
and&#13;
EDOS_1.0_2.1-M10_New&#13;
have been uploaded.</PreCondition>
    <PostCondition>No Post-Conditions.</PostCondition>
    <TestObjectives>Demonstrate capability to support a MO4 initial load message for panels and atomic tests.&#13;
Demonstrate capability to support all supported data elements, including repeating fields in the CDM segment.&#13;
Demonstrate capability to support a NTE segment.</TestObjectives>
    <Notes>No Notes.</Notes>
    <Comments>Initial upload of charge codes (CPT codes) for orderable tests and panels for a new compendium.  &#13;
Since this is a replace message, all data in this message will replace information from a previous eDOS M04 message</Comments>
</TestCaseMetaData>
