<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TestCaseMetaData xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" id="LRI_0.0_1.1-NG" date="11/02/2016" name="Smoke test" version="20161102">
		<Description>Mr. Hector Ramos is a 81 year old Hispanic male who is on warfarin therapy.  Mr. Ramos presents to  Good Health Clinic to see Dr. Radon for a routine check up.   The doctor orders a Prothrombin Time (PT + INR) test from the clinical lab at Century Hospital using the clinic's EHR system and instruct Mr. Ramos to go to the laboratory's patient service center to have the blood sample collected.   The laboratory performs the requested test and the final result was  10.5  sec with a ref range of 9.5-13.8 sec  and the INR calculated to be 1.0    {INR}   with a  normal reference range being 0.8 and 1.2 {INR}.  The final result report for this lab test was generated by the LIS and transmitted to the patient's record in the Good health Clinic's EHR system.</Description>
		<PreCondition>No Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>No Post Condition.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Minimally populated message.
Demonstrate ability to support creating  a  lab result message with all required data elements for the test case:
Minimally populated MSH Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the MSH segment.
Minimally populated PID Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the PID segment.
Minimally populated ORC Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the ORC segment.
Minimally populated OBR Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the OBR segment.
Minimally populated OBX Segment - Demonstrate the capability to support the minimally required data elements in the OBX segment.</TestObjectives>
		<Notes>No Notes.</Notes>
		<Comments>This is the initial "smoke testing" to reveal simple failures of the result message severe enough to preclude further testing.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>