<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TestCaseMetaData xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" id="EDOS_1.0_1.1-M08_NG" date="11/18/2015" name="MO8_New" version="version3">
		<Description>
The initial Laboratory Test Compendium built by Century Hospital Clinical Laboratory is a subset of their Directory of Services.  It is based upon the most commonly ordered lab tests by Dr. Radon.
This compendium is delivered electronically to Dr. Nicholas Radon's practice EHR, as agreed to between Laboratory and Dr. Radon's Office and EHR-S Vendor.   The EHR-S will integrate the eDOS into its test directory and use it to allow Dr. Radon to place orders electronically to Century Hospital's Clinical Laboratory.   
The initial laboratory test compendium is composed of five messages.
Century Hospital's LIS transmit the first message which provides information about each resultable observation.</Description>
		<PreCondition>No Pre-Condition.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>No Post-Condition.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate capability to support a M08 initial load message for numeric, calculated, qualitative and narrative tests.
Demonstrate capability to support all supported data elements, including repeating fields in the MSH segment.
Demonstrate capability to support all supported data elements, including repeating fields in the MF1 segment. 
Demonstrate capability to support all supported data elements, including repeating fields in the OM1 - not each OM1 segment will be maximally populated or include repeating fields (OM1-52 is covered in EDOS_2.2).
Demonstrate capability to support all supported data elements, including repeating fields in the OMC segment.
Demonstrate capability to support repeating segments for OMC.
Demonstrate capability to support all supported data elements, including repeating fields in the OM2 segment.
Demonstrate capability to support all supported data elements, including repeating fields in the OM3 segment.
Demonstrate capability to support all supported data elements, including repeating fields in the OM4 segment.
Demonstrate capability to support repeating segments for OM4.</TestObjectives>
		<Comments>Initial upload of individual observations for a new compendium.
Since this is a replace message, all data in this message will replace information from a previous eDOS M08 message.
Demonstrate capability to support sending ask at order entry requirements.
Demonstrate capability to define the specimen requirements.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>