<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TestCaseMetaData xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" id="EDOS_1.0_3.1-M04_NG" date="11/18/2015" name="M04_New" version="version3">
		<Description>
The initial Laboratory Test Compendium built by Century Hospital Clinical Laboratory is a subset of their Directory of Services.  It is based upon the most commonly ordered lab tests by Dr. Radon.  This compendium is delivered electronically to Dr. Nicholas Radon's practice EHR, as agreed to between Laboratory and Dr. Radon's Office and EHR-S Vendor.   The EHR-S will integrate the eDOS into its test directory and use it to allow Dr. Radon to place orders electronically to Century Hospital's Clinical Laboratory.   
The initial laboratory test compendium is composed of five messages.  
After Century Hospital's LIS successfully transmits the first and second messages which provide information about each individual observation and each orderable battery or profile,  it sends the third message which provides information about CPT procedure codes for each orderable panel and individual observation.</Description>
		<PreCondition>EDOS_1.0_1.1-M08_New
and
EDOS_1.0_2.1-M10_New
have been uploaded.</PreCondition>
		<PostCondition>No Post-Condition.</PostCondition>
		<TestObjectives>Demonstrate capability to support a M04 initial load message for panels and atomic tests.
Demonstrate capability to support NTE segments, including repeats under one MFI.
Demonstrate capability to support NTE segments, including repeats under one MFE.
Demonstrate capability to support all supported data elements, including repeating fields in the CDM segment.
Demonstrate capability to support NTE segments, including repeats under one CDM.</TestObjectives>
		<Comments>Initial upload of charge codes (CPT codes) for orderable tests and panels for a new compendium.  
Since this is a replace message, all data in this message will replace information from a previous eDOS M04 message.
Demonstrate capability to support multiple instances of procedure code for a single test.</Comments>
	</TestCaseMetaData>